《越狱》第四季 第十七集
Prison.Break.S04E17
《越狱》  前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
你妈妈为我们工作
Your mother works for us.
她还活着
Your mother is alive.
我越想越觉得 这是有人监守自盗
You know, i'm thinking more and more that this Is an inside job. why?
他带去见面的仪器 可以当场读取里面的内容
The hardware he brought to the meet. He could read scylla right on the spot.
把手举起来
Hands on your head.
我们得赶快离开这里
We've got to get out of here!
迈克尔  上车
Michael. Get in!
现在  比起钱 我更想过我自己的生活
Sorry, but right now i want my life back More than i want your money.
"锡拉"在哪里
Where's scylla?
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk about that, okay?
在什么地方
Where is it?
我能拿回来
I can get it.
他不会拿来的
No, he can't.
他在拖延时间  林肯
He's stalling, linc.
-拿不回来了  -你说对了
it's gone. you're right.
你真不知道他为谁工作
You have no idea who this guy's working for?
是的
No, no clue.
你的人已经死了
Your boy's dead.
现在
And now
我要找你算账
I'm coming after you.
刚才是谁
Who was that?
我儿子
It was my son.
林肯
Lincoln.
林肯收
这是什么东西
What is this?
我也不知道
I don't know...
就放在门外
Just found them on the doorstep.
狗娘养的
Son of a...
他们要是敢动我妈一根头发  我保证...
They lay one hand on my mama, i swear on my life...
她在老家
She's in a state home.
我以为我们是和这些人合作
I thought we were working with these people.
我也是这么想的
So did i.
我去打个电话
I'm gonna make a call.
看看到底是怎么回事
Find out what's going on.
布伦斯先生
Mr. burrows.
我们说好的
We had a deal.
协议上说的是要找回"锡拉"
Our deal is contingent upon the retrieval of scylla.
根据你现在的表现
Based on the mediocrity of your performance
从现在开始
On that front thus far,
我认为  你们需要 更大的动力
I thought it best to make sure you're all properly motivated
告诉我你们进展如何了
Just tell me how your team is progressing.
我对天发誓
I swear to god, man, when i,
你要是栽倒我手里
When i get a hold of you...
如果我是你
If i were you,
我现在会想尽一切办法 证明我的能力
I'd be doing everything in my power To demonstrate my competence right now.
我们在迈阿密杀了一个人
We killed the guy who came to miami.
我们发现几把钥匙
We found some keys on him.
我们还在查
We're looking into them.
还有其他事情吗
Are we done?
还没有
Not quite.
有个新的竞争者 也加入了我们的行列
A new competitor Has joined the search.
我们一定会得到"锡拉"
We're the ones getting scylla.
很高兴你能这么说
Well, that's good to hear,
因为竞争者正是你的弟弟迈克尔
Because the competing party, is your brother michael.
迈克尔一直和你在一起
Michael's with you.
迈克尔是你救的
Michael's getting treatment. With you.
显然  迈克尔比我们想的更执着
Apparently michael's a little more headstrong than either of us imagined.
但是别担心
But don't worry.
我们已经在亚利桑那找到他的线索
We have a lead on him somewhere in central arizona.
鄂伦先生在他车里等你
Mr. oren is waiting in his limousine.
如果你能和迈克尔通话
If you speak to michael,
告诉他  好好地躲起来
Tell him to find a very good hiding place.
如果我们的人发现了他
Because if any of my men spot him,
格杀勿论
They've been given a green light.
还要走2500英里
2,500 miles to go.
如果我们换班开车 明天晚上就能到
If we take turns sleeping We can be there by tomorrow night.
要不要给林肯打电话  告诉他我们要去
Should we call lincoln? let him know we're coming?
迈克尔  他是为了救你 才和公司做交易
Michael, he took the company's deal To save your life.
如果我是他  我也会这么做
And for what it's worth, i might've done the same thing.
你们都错了
Then you'd be wrong, too.
我们要开挺长时间的车
You know, this promises to be a really, really long ride.
我们还是
So, how about we just...
暂时停战吧
Call truce, all right?
忘了拿餐巾纸
Forgot napkins.
趴下
Get down.
快走
Come on.
他如果敢动我孩子...
He comes anywhere near my kid...
唐  说实话
You know, don,
你貌似对这件事反应不大
You seem to be taking this whole thing pretty well.
我是个很冷静的人
Yeah, well, i'm a pretty calm guy.
我的意思是
All i'm saying is,
我妈妈  他儿子  还有他老婆
My mama, his son, his wife.
我们都不知道他拿什么威胁你
We don't even know who they got on you.
这和你们没关系
That's 'cause it's none of your business.
你只要知道
All right, all you need to worry about
我在这里是为了完成这个工作
Is that i'm here to do a job.
"稳锁"
Hold-secure.
钥匙生产商的名字
The company that manufactures the keys.
叫"稳锁"  你们听听
It's called hold-secure. listen to this.
每把钥匙都植入了一个电脑芯片
Each key they produce is implanted with a computer chip.
芯片会发出独一无二的
That chip sends out a unique
电子信号打开相应的锁
Electronic signal that opens its lock.
非常高科技
Something that high-tech,
我觉得  他们一定有资料库
I'm telling you, i'm betting they got a database
我们可以查到每把钥匙
That'll tell us exactly where each key's
匹配的锁是在哪里安装的
Corresponding lock has been installed.
看看这个
Look at that.
每把钥匙就要500块钱
These keys run about 500 bucks each?!
如果不是保护重要物品
You only spend that kind of money if you're
谁会买这玩意儿
Protecting something of vital importance.
"锡拉"
Like scylla.
刚刚有人尝试进入
Someone just tried to access
卡鲁斯在"稳锁"的帐号
Carruth's account at hold-secure.
有什么被暴露了
And what information was compromised?
我们还不知道
We don't know yet.
是谁干的
And who was trying to access it?
也不知道
We don't know.
谢谢你提醒我  很好
Thank you for bringing that to my attention. good work.
说
Yes?
是你的儿子
It's your son.
我们已经派人对付林肯了
We already have safeguards in place to deal with lincoln.
我是说迈克尔
I'm talking about michael.
他从公司里逃了出来
He's escaped company custody.
他在来迈阿密的路上
He's coming to miami right now.
克里斯汀娜
Christina?
他们要是知道我的目的就行
If only they understood what it is i'm trying to do.
谢谢
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
现在怎么办
Okay, what now?
我们会想出办法的
We'll think of something.
迈克尔  我们买不起车
Michael, we can't afford to buy a car
也不能坐飞机
And we can't fly.
该给你哥哥打电话了
It's time to call your brother.
明白
Got it.
我们找到那两把锁的位置了
We've got the locations of those two locks.
一个在小哈瓦那
One's in little havana.
另外一个在海边
The other one's down by the water.
好极了  林肯  你和我...
Perfect. lincoln, why don't you and i...
你和赛尔夫一起去小哈瓦那
You take self and go to little havana.
我们去另一边
We're gonna head south.
不是吧
Huh, that's a surprise.
我们要带点防晒霜
We need suntan lotion.
马上就来
Be right there.
是我
It's me.
你搞什么鬼
What's your problem?
林肯  你必须听我解释
Look, i need you to hear me out on this, linc.
你把所有计划都给毁了
Everything was all set up and you blew it.
你就是不想让我来处理  对吗
You couldn't just let me handle this, could you?
如果你说的是把"锡拉"给将军
If by "handle," you mean give scylla back to the general,
你说对了
Then no, i couldn't.
这件事情很复杂
It's more complicated than that.
其实不是
Actually, it's not.
听我说
Listen to me,
我想过我自己的生活
I want my life back
这是我们唯一的一条出路
And this is the only way we can do that!
我不同意你的想法
I don't believe that's true.
说句心里话 你能不能成熟点
You know what, man? You need to grow up.
如果你真是这么想的
Look, if that's how you really feel, linc,
我警告你  我会用尽一切方法 阻止你
I should warn you i'm going to do everything in my power To stop you.
我和将军已经有了协议
I had a deal with the general.
你却给搞砸了
You blew it.
一旦他发现你  就会杀了你
He finds you, he's gonna kill you.
我早就知道
Surprise, surprise.
我是为了我们才这么做的
I did this for us, michael.
你  我  莎拉
You, me, sara,
还有Lj  这样你才能和莎拉在一起
Lj, so you could be with sara.
你好好为你的家人想想
Two seconds, just think of your family.
我这几天能考虑的
Feels like family's the only thing
只有我的家人了
I can think about these days.
你什么意思
What does that mean?
迈克尔
Michael?
林肯  妈妈还活着
Linc, mom is alive.
什么
What?
到了迈阿密再说
Guess i'll see you in miami.
我们要赶快离开这里
We gotta get out of here.
先生  介意我问你去哪里吗
Sir, you mind if i ask where you're going?
达拉斯
Dallas.
我们能搭个车吗
Mind if we hitch a ride?
我有100块油钱
I got 100 bucks; gas money.
求你了
Please?
先生
Sir?
驾驶室不够三个人坐
Cab's not big enough for the two of you.
如果你们想一起搭车
If you want to ride together
你们就得坐货柜里
You're going to have to ride back here.
成交
Done.
坐舒服了
Get comfortable.
下次停车  要等八个小时
Gonna be eight hours till we stop again.
林肯
Linc...
如果"锡拉"在这里  警卫会有很多
If scylla really is in there, there's gonna be security.
你要集中精神
I need you focused.
好
Yeah.
楼上安全
All Clear upstairs.
你发现什么了
You find something?
我妈的照片
Picture of my mom.
有人知道我一定会来
Someone must have known i was coming.
肯定是和卡鲁斯联系密切的人
Someone who's connected enough to be working with carruth
而且是非常了解你
And who knows you well enough
才可能拿到那张照片
To get their hands on that picture.
只有一个人 符合刚才说的标准
There's only one person i can think of That fits that description.
你的意思是我妈妈在迈阿密
You're saying my mom's in miami?
如果她在其他地方指挥
If she was operating out of this house,
资金对她来说一定不是问题
She certainly had access to money.
她是公司的特工
She's a company agent.
格雷琴说过  她认为 是公司内部人干的
Gretchen said she thought That this could be an inside job.
林肯
Linc...
你妈妈有可能控制着"锡拉"
Your mother could have scylla.
以前  我们放学的时候 她会烤饼干给我们
She used to bake cookies when we'd come home From school,
在后院和我们一起踢球
Play kickball with us in the backyard.
她不可能是特工
There's just no way that woman was a company agent.
你看了她的资料  对吗
You did read her file, didn't you?
我看了医疗报告
I saw medical reports
上面说她和我做过同样的检查
That said she had the same diagnosis i did
公司的医生也 给她做了手术
And that company doctors operated On her, too.
我一直在想  之后他们是否也带她
Now i'm wondering if they took her off
去了那座小木屋
To a log cabin in the woods after they were done,
给她介绍一个神经科医生
Introduced her to a friendly shrink.
怎么会有人看着自己的孩子
How else could someone just stand by and watch
像落水狗一样让人追杀
Their own children were hunted down like dogs?
可能她不知道
Maybe she didn't know.
她早就知道
She knew.
可能她没办法处理
Maybe it was over her head.
或者她根本不在乎
Or maybe she didn't care.
我只是很惊讶
Anyway, i'm just surprised
将军等了这么长时间  才告诉我们这个秘密
The general waited so long to drop this bomb on us.
其实  我觉得很合情合理
Actually, i think that part makes sense.
不管是什么原因
I mean, for whatever reason,
你妈妈不想让你们知道她还活着
Your mother didn't want you to know she was alive
否则你们可能早就知道了
Or you would have known years ago.
将军只是保守秘密
The general was just keeping that secret, right?
让她高兴  让她卖命
Keeping her happy, keeping her working.
但是  现在情况不同了
But now the game has changed.
他认为现在可以利用你了
Yeah, now he thinks you might be useful.
就像我妈一样
Just like mom.
毫无疑问  他是我接触过的
Beyond question, he possesses the most gifted mind
最天资聪颖的人
Of any man i've ever encountered.
我尽量不带那么多个人情绪
Well, i'll try not to take that too personally.
他钻孔到你的办公室保险箱
He drilled into your office safe
神不知鬼不觉地复制了你的卡
And copied your card without you even noticing.
回想起来  你当时坐在我旁边吧
As I recall, you were sitting right next to me.
如果我们能招纳迈克尔・斯科菲尔德
If we could have turned Michael Scofield,
就能多利用克里斯汀娜30年
It would have been like having 30 more years of Christina.
靠边停下
Pull over.
我的车在那
That's my ride.
怎么了
What's going on?
再见  乔纳森
Good-bye, Jonathan.
不是这里
This isn't the place.
我用假手都能开那种锁
I could pick that lock with my stump.
不  不
No, n-no, n-no.
这就叫表里不一
Remember what they say about books and their covers.
海瑞・温斯顿把希望之星
When Harry Winston donated the hope diamond
捐给史密森尼博物馆时  你知道他怎么
To the smithsonian, you know how he got it from new york
把它从纽约带到华盛顿吗
To dc?
挂号信
Registered mail.
这是最安全的方式
It's the safest way to go.
毕竟  没人会去邮局
After all, who is going to be looking
查找希望之星
For the hope diamond at the post office, right?
又有谁会到小哈瓦那
And who would be looking for scylla
的一个破烂教堂
At some run-down storefront church
-找"锡拉"呢  -就算你说得对
- In little havana?- All right, let's say you're right.
他们把"锡拉"放里面了
They got scylla back there somewhere.
你进去跟臭保安拼命
You walk in there, reeking that cop stink,
坚持不了多久
You won't last a second.
说得对
That's a good point.
所以由你去
That's why you're going in.
能帮您什么吗
May i help you?
是的  事实上
Yes, as a matter of fact.
我是查尔斯・帕特西
I'm Charles Patoshik.
我是南福罗里达大学的
I'm a professor of anthropology
人类学教授
At southern florida university.
我正在研究不同种类的
I'm doing some various research on various different kinds
加勒比宗教
Of, uh, uh, uh, caribbean religions, and, uh...
或许可以
Perhaps you could start
从里面开始
Back there where you, you do your, uh, services.
那是我们的圣堂
That is our sanctuary.
只有纯洁的心灵 方可进入
Only the pure of soul May venture inside.
了解
I know.
我去过很多圣堂
I-i have been in many such rooms.
让我看看你的手
Let me see your hand.
你心灵不纯
Your soul is black,
沾有无辜人的鲜血
Stained with the blood of the innocent.
我不能让你进去
I cannot let you pass.
从来没有人这么冒犯过我
I have never been so offended in my life.
我建议  你去别处
I suggest that you continue your research
继续研究
Elsewhere.
如果是不小心
If you drop something
落下的东西
By accident,
上面肯定会有指纹
You leave a fingerprint on it.
她就想让你发现这个
She wanted you to find this.
-为什么  -你以前看过吗
Why? you ever seen it before?
没有
No.
你还记得
Do you remember
那天的事吗
Anything about that day?
我当时4岁
I was four years old.
记得在哪拍的吗
Any idea where it was taken?
忘了
No.
没事吧
You okay?
-如果我发现我妈妈  -听着
I mean, if i found out my mom was... listen,
就我而言  她不是我妈
As far as i'm concerned, she's not my mom.
只是我自由路上的绊脚石
She's just someone in the way of my freedom.
懂了吗
All right?
我6岁生日时
So, on my sixth birthday,
爸爸已经离开很长时间了
Um, my father was long gone by then,
只剩下我  妈妈   林肯
So it was just me, mom, and linc, and...
妈妈送给我礼物
Mom hands me my present--
我唯一的礼物  我以为...
My, uh, my only present-- and i just know...
我猜那是千年隼号的模型
I just know it's the millennium falcon.
有战斗警报声的吗
With the battle alert sound?
没错
Exactly.
-我有过一样的  -当然
-I totally owned that. -of course you did.
我为这个求了母亲好几个礼拜
Anyway, i had been asking for this thing for weeks,
包装的大小看起来一模一样
And the package is just the right size, and...
我撕下包装
I rip open the wrapping paper
结果却是个鸟巢
And... it's a birdhouse.
不
Oh, no.
其实不算是个鸟巢
Oh, yeah, except it's not even a birdhouse.
是一套鸟巢玩具包
It's actually a birdhouse kit.
真是遗憾
I'm so sorry.
之后两天我都没和她说话
I didn't talk to her for two days after that,
但她最后还是想办法让我开始拼
But when she finally got me to open the thing,
我们坐在一起
We sat there together,
一块一块的拼起来
Put it together piece by piece,
那是我的第一个建筑作品
And it was the first thing i ever built.
我很喜欢它
And i loved it...
她一早就知道我会喜欢上它
And she knew i would.
她比我更加了解我自己
She knew me better than i knew myself.
母亲的天性
That's what moms do.
奇怪的是
Yeah, but the strange thing is...
即使我们有23年没见
Even though i haven't seen her for 23 years,
我仍然能感觉到
There's this part of me
她依然是如此
That feels like maybe she still does.
你的车好像有些超载
Your truck looks a little low to the ground.
介意下车来看看吗
You mind stepping outside?
我刚刚才在20英里外磅重过
I just got weighed 20 miles back.
你是高速公路巡警吗
You highway patrol?
去哪里
Where are you going?
这和你无关
You've got no business in there.
除非你有搜查令
Unless you show me a warrant,
否则马上滚下来
You get the hell out of there right now.
谢谢
Thank you.
上帝
Goodness.
我有磅重点的票据
I got my weigh station ticket
就在我的车上
Right here on the dash.
给你看看
As soon as you see that...
我刚刚才磅过重的
You'll see i got it right here.
给
Here you go.
我要你跟着我回凤凰城
I need you to follow me back to phoenix.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我要去达拉斯卸货
I got to get this load to dallas.
这是你自己选的
Well, that's your choice.
找到他们了
I got 'em.
我们该给你哥哥打电话
I think we need to call your brother.
没信号
No signal.
我们肯定在鸟不生蛋的地方
We must be in the middle of nowhere.
林肯说如果公司抓到你的话
Lincoln said that if the company caught you...
我看到这里有个侧门
I think i saw a side door back here.
为何不走正门
What about the main door?
不可能打开了
You'll never get that open.
肯定从外面锁上了
I'm sure it's latched from the outside.
侧门能开吗
Can you open the side door?
也许
Maybe.
莎拉
Sara.
帮我一下
Help me out.
我们搬不动这个
I don't think we're going to be able to move this.
我们不用搬
Maybe we won't have to.
我有个关于克兰兹将军的坏消息
I have troubling news about general krantz.
他还活着
He's alive.
这不可能
I don't see how that's possible.
但我听说有一架
Yes, well, what i'm hearing is a
从公司洛城总部起飞的
helicopter with
直升飞机在一小时前
From company headquarters in los angeles one hour ago.
抵达郊区峡谷
It landed for two minutes in canyon country
正在返回洛城途中
And now it's back in los angeles.
你找到他的尸体了吗
So you got the corpse?
直升机降落在公司总部
The helicopter landed back at company headquarters.
你知道除掉他对我们努力
You know how important getting rid of him is
达到的目标有多重要
To what we're trying to accomplish.
好吧  我可以搞定
All right, I can still get this done.
时间不够了
Not in our time frame.
好吧  我要速战速决
All right, I'm pulling the plug.
我们要着手处理结果了
We need to start dealing with the consequences.
等会儿  关键的是
Wait, wait, wait. first things first.
他知道我已经背叛了他
He knows that i've betrayed him.
我需要消失
I need to disappear.
直觉真敏锐
I think that's a good instinct.
我在森瓦利有间房子
I have a house in Sun Valley.
我还有个主意
I have another idea.
你介意打开扬声器吗
Do you mind putting me on speaker?
格里夫  你是个勇敢的人
You know, Griff, you're a brave man.
我感谢你为我做的每一件事
And I thank you for everything you've done.
这是你的荣耀
It's been an honor.
现在
Now.
现在什么
"Now" what?
照片里的汽车是佛罗里达的牌照
The car in this picture has Florida plates.
你去那儿度过假吗
Did you ever vacation there?
-没有  -你认不认识
- No.  - Do you know anyone
-从那来拜访的人吗  -不认识
- From Forida who came up to visit?  - No.
他们为什么要在那辆车前拍照
Why did they take this picture in front of that car?
我们没有拍过
We didn't.
照片被修改过了
It's been doctored.
这一点我不能肯定
I'm not sure about that.
光线  影子 都处理地很好
I mean, the lighting, the shadows, All sync up perfectly.
这是78年版的西风
This is a '78 zephyr.
迈克尔76年出生
Michael was born in '76.
你是唯一能想起来的人
You're the only one who could've picked up on that.
这照片是特意为你修改的
She doctored that for you.
看看她还可能修改了什么
Let's see what else she might've changed.
那辆西风的牌照是什么
What's the license plate on that zephyr?
M-I-K 4-4-1
M-I-K 4-4-1.
马丁路德金大道与411道路交叉口处
Martin Luther King boulevard intersects with route 441
大概离这里偏北五英里
About five miles north of here.
很好
Good.
你们在这里  我们在小哈瓦那
You guys are here. listen, we're a little outmanned
人手不够  你们可以支援我们
Down in Little Havana. we could use some backup.
我们有买家的线索
We got a lead on the buyer.
很好  那我们还等什么
Great, what are we waiting for?
我还是自己干吧
I think I gonna do it myself.
我们应该在一起  团队合作嘛
Come on, let's stay together. we're a team, right?
-我说过我能做到  -经过今早的
- I said i got it.  - After our little
小小特殊快递
Special deliveries this morning,
每个人都是平等的了
Each one of us has an equal stake.
无论谁牵的头  我们都要让他们出局
Whoever started this, we're all going to take them out.
我们认为买家是林肯的母亲
The buyer, we think it's Lincoln's mother.
你说什么
What?
正如我所说  我自己干
Like i said, i'm doing this myself.
林肯
Linc!
如果她有"锡拉"
If she has scylla,
她是不会拱手相让的
She's not just going to hand it over
与将军相比是有过之而无不及
Any more than the general would have.
你也不知道
You don't know that.
我们都认为拿着"锡拉"的人
We always thought whoever had scylla
会像将军那样做事
Would do what the general did.
也许她不会
Maybe she won't.
你当真吗
Are you serious?
你妈是公司特工
Your mother is a company agent?
她曾经是
She was.
她现在可能是个好人了
She might be one of the good guys now.
恕我直言
With all due respect,
我觉得你没有把握
I don't think you're in a place where you can make
断定这点
A clear determination about that.
这个MLK 441可能什么也不是
Listen, this MLK 441 could be nothing.
但在那座教堂里
But at the church,
可能会有"锡拉"
There could be scylla.
如果需要你帮助  我会打电话
If i need you, i'll call.
这应该管用
This should work.
克里斯汀娜
Christina?
你有必要知道在过去24小时中
You need to acknowledge that our chance
我们成功的几率大大降低了
Of success has substantially declined in the last 24 hours.
有人在追查我们
There are people out looking for us.
要开始考虑退路了
We need to start thinking in terms of contingencies.
再等等  就几天
Just a little while longer, only a few more days.
克兰兹将军面对严重威胁时
General Krantz refused to adjust
也拒绝调整
When there were credible threats against him.
所以我们才夺取"锡拉"
That's the reason we have scylla now.
你不会拿我和他相提并论吧
Are you honestly comparing me to him?
我知道在整件事中你给自己的定位
I understand what you think your role is in all of this,
也很感谢你的努力
And I appreciate your efforts.
但如果你觉得
But if you can't tell the difference
我和他一样  你就去找将军
Between he and I, perhaps you need to ask
要回你的职位
The general for your old job back.
瞧
Oh, look.
是他打的  你想接吗
Here he is. would you like to take the call?
乔纳森
Jonathan.
下午好  克里斯汀娜
Good afternoon, Christina.
听到你的声音真高兴
It's good to hear your voice.
我想这意味着你找到"锡拉"了
I assume this means you've retrieved scylla.
还没
Not yet.
真糟糕
Oh, troubling news.
知道它在哪吗
Have any idea where it is?
你在哪  克里斯汀娜
Where are you, Christina?
约翰内斯堡  我还能在哪呢
Johannesburg. where else would I be?
我让附近的部下
I've had some of my contacts
到你家去查看
In your area check on your house.
家里没有人
There's no one home.
当然没有  没找到"锡拉"
Well, of course not. as long as scylla's in play,
那个地址就是假的
That address is blown.
你在哪  克里斯汀娜
Where are you, Christina?
我不喜欢你的语气  乔纳森
I don't like your tone, jonathan.
如果语气不好
Excuse me
请原谅
If I sound a bit abrasive.
但刚刚有人想杀我
But it's been a while since anyone's tried to kill me.
天哪
Oh, my god.
你没事吧  发生什么事了
Are you all right? what happened?
鄂伦
Oren.
"Oren"?
我们找到了他的尸体  他杀
We found his body... executed.
我只能想到他是和别人共事的
I can only assume that he's working with someone.
某个不用承受失败的人
Someone who doesn't tolerate failure.
你到底在哪  克里斯汀娜
Now, where are you, Christina?
你听我说
You listen to me.
如果你想说我和这事有关
If you're implying that I had anything to do with this...
你在哪里
Where are you?
我为公司付出了这么多  我丈夫  孩子
After everything i've given to the compeny. My husband, my children...
我想是时候我们坐下来
I think it's time that we had a sit-down.
-好好谈谈  -我告诉你
- And talk.  - Tell you what.
干嘛不召集你的亲信
Why don't you gether up the brain trust,
你的笨女儿和病态情人
That half-witted daughter and your psychotic mistress?
召集起来想想锡拉的去向
Why don't you get together and figure out where scylla is?
然后再打给我
Then call me.
布伦斯先生
Mr. Burrows.
我能带您去您的座位吗
May I escort you to your table?
你一点都没变
You haven't changed a bit.
很高兴你收到了我的信息
I'm glad you got my message.
我知道这不是最直接的交流方式
I know it wasn't the most straightforward
但我要确定那是你
Mode of communication, but I had to be sure it was you.
至少我知道迈克尔怎么得到的
At least now I know where Michael gets it from.
你肯定有很多问题想问
I'm sure you have many questions.
"锡拉"在哪
Where's scylla?
它很安全
It's safe.
现在我只能说这么多
That's all I can tell you for right now.
那我们就没什么可说的了
Then we've got nothing to talk about.
真的吗
Really?
你来就是为了这个吗
That's the only reason you came here?
对
Yeah.
我一直以为你想知道真相
I really would've thought you wanted to know the truth.
我已经知道了
I know the truth.
你为公司效力
You work for the company.
那群用谋杀案陷害我的家伙
The same people that set me up for murder.
-林肯  -还是那群人
- Lincoln...  - The same people
自从我们从福克斯河监狱越狱之后
That have been trying to kill me and Michael
就一直追杀我和迈克尔
Ever since we escaped Fox River.
你可以随便猜测  但我不是个恶魔
You can think it as much as you want, I'm not a monster.
23年过去了  你连道歉都没有
23 years and not even an apology?
如果道歉可以管用的话
If I thought an apology would do any good,
我肯定会道歉
I would offer it.
求你了
Please.
请你坐下
Please sit down.
抛弃你们兄弟俩
Leaving you two boys...
是我这辈子最艰难的决定
Was the hardest thing I ever did.
你还是做了
But you did.
你一走了之去为公司效力
And then you went off and worked for the company.
你以为你了解那个公司
You know, you think you know what the company is,
实际上你根本不了解
But you don't.
公司的意志是受首脑控制的
It is a body that bends to the will of its head.
它现在既好战又嗜血
And right now, it is bloodthirsty and war-hungry,
因为克兰兹将军就是这种人
Because that's who General Krantz is.
但如果一个女人
But what if a woman,
一位母亲掌管公司
A mother, ran it?
你能想象会有多大的改变吗
Can you imagine the different that would make?
你以为你是位母亲
You think you're a mother?
母亲的首要职责 是照顾家庭
A mother's priority Is her family.
如果我把"锡拉"给将军  他就会
If I give scylla back to the general, he leaves me
放过我和迈克尔  我就可以多花些时间
And Michael alone, and I get to spend time
安安静静地陪我儿子
With my son in peace.
要向你解释我为什么这么做  做了什么
Look, I could sit here for days and try to explain to you
可能花上几天时间
Why I did what I did.
简单地说  我就不能保护你了
Suffice it to say, I couldn't protect you then,
但是现在请让我保护你
But let me protect you now.
如果克兰兹将军死了
What if general Krantz were no longer in the picture?
一旦解决了他
Once he is dealt with,
就没有人再追杀你们了
No one would come after you.
但是我需要时间  林肯
But I need time, Lincoln.
我需要两天时间
I need two days
去把一切安排妥当
To put everything into place.
如果你能给我两天时间
If you give me two days...
我就能让你和迈克尔
...then I can give you and Michael
拥有充分彻底的自由
Your complete and utter freedom.
好吧
All right.
我现在就开始动手
I'm going to get started right away.
如果克兰兹产生怀疑的话
But if Krantz suspects any of this,
他不会放过我们俩的
He's going to hunt us both down.
正因如此
And for that reason,
在一切办完之前
I can't risk being seen with you
不能让人发现你我见面了
Until all of this is over.
那我怎么联系你
How will I get in touch with you?
你不能联系我
You can't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
只要把这个箱子拉倒
Once we pull this box down,
就能压倒售水机
It'll push the water machine
撞开侧门
Right through the side door.
车子减速了  我们肯定下了高速公路
We're slowing down. I think we're getting off the highway.
快弄好了
I'm almost ready.
莎拉  抓住那边的带子
Sara, grab that strap over there.
好的  抓住
All right, hold it.
快点
Come on!
你没事吧
You all right?
你解决那个区域之后
After you clear the area
我就不会遇到任何阻碍了
I don't anticipate any problems.
懂了吗
All right?
放手一搏了
Scylla or not here we come.
好的  等等
All right. hold on.
这些人要干什么
What the hell are those guys doing?
我们无法对付更多人
We're not going against any additional people in there.
-等他们出来  -好的
- We wait until they come back out.  - All right.
林肯的妈妈真的是买家吗
So Lincoln's mother is really the buyer?
看来是的
It appears that way.
我希望他能理解
I hope he understands,
如果需要除掉她才能拿到锡拉
That if I need to take her out to get to scylla,
我会毫不犹豫地杀了她
I'm not going to hesitate to kill her.
同意
No question.
希望不要走到这步
Well, let's just hope it doesn't come to that.
你说真的吗
You serious?
我认真的  如果不用杀掉林肯的妈妈
Yeah. am I serious if we can get scylla
就能拿到锡拉的话
Without killing Linc's mother,
这样更好
That's the preferable outcome.
等等
Wait a second.
如果我要和你一起深入虎穴
If I'm gonna be in the foxhole with you,
我要知道你真的能帮我
I need to know that you have my back.
东西在布伦斯夫人手里
Mrs. Burrows has the item,
拿到它的唯一方法就是杀了她
And the only way to get it is to kill her.
你打算怎么做
What is your move?
我会开枪
I pull the trigger.
他们走了  咱们走吧
There they go, Come on.
唐・赛尔夫
Don self,
国土安全局的
Homeland Security.
我们正在调查 一起虐待动物的案件
We're investigating A cruelty to animal charge.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're referring to.
在祭祀典礼上大量屠杀鸡群
We're referring to ritual Slaughters of chickens.
你们国家可能允许
Okay, that might be allowed where you come from
但在美国  不允许
But here in America, that's no mas.
鸡吗  太可笑了
Chickens? This is preposterous.
就因为我是加勒比人
This is because I'm Caribbean.
我发誓  我闻到鸡血腥味了
I swear to god, I smelled chicken blood.
比我们封锁的那条街 味道还重
Worse than the place Down the street we shut down.
你想把事情搞大吗
You want to turn this into something?
坐下
Sit down.
如果这没什么鸡 那就是没有
If there aren't any chickens, There aren't any chickens.
但我们必须搜一下 才能知道
But we're not going to know that Until we take a look around.
气味从后面发出来
The smell was coming from back there.
那是我们的圣堂
That is our sanctuary.
我不能让你进去玷污它
I cannot let you to disrupt it.
我理解  但我还是要进去
I understand your concerns, but I need to go back there.
不行  你不能这么做
I insist, you cannot do that.
你可以一起过去  只能做到这了
Best I can do is have you accompany us, please.
走吧
Please.
你
You,
快走  到外面去 等他们完事
Come on, let's go outside Until they're done.
走吧
Let's go.
这可不是什么神圣的事
That's not a very heavenly thing to do.
安全通行证
找到什么了吗
Find anything?
是的
Oh, yeah.
他们在这干什么
What the hell are they up to?
我不知道
I don't know.
那个男的只说要租间储物室
He just asked to rent that closet.
有个女人和他来过吗
Did a woman ever come down here with him?
来过一次
Yeah, once.
我都告诉你了
I'm telling you,
我只知道这些
That's all I know.
放下枪
Drop it.
别动
Don't.
过来  你们两个
Come here. Both of you,
跪下
On your knees.
听见了没  跪下
I said on your knees.
我告诉过你不要进来
I told you not to come in here.
还有一个人哪去了
Where's the other guy?
他跑了  我们快走
He ran. Let's go.
我们走
Let's go.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
还好
Yeah.
快走
Let's go.
快点
Come on.
我们没法回车上了
We're not going to make it back to the truck.
我知道
I know.
给
Here.
拿着这个
Take this.
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
迈克尔
Michael.
Michael!
你还好吗
You all right?
还好  谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
将军现在该知道不要和我们作对了
The general should know by now not to mess with us.
不是... 将军派我来的
The general... Didn't send me.
谁派的
Who did?
谁派你来的
Who sent you?
林肯
Lincoln!
我们有新线索了
We've got news.
我也有
So do I.
我们这两天不要行动
We're staying low for two days.
克里斯汀娜承诺过要摆脱克兰兹
Christina's promised to get rid of Krantz.
我觉得她在撒谎
I think she's lying.
我知道这听起来很疯狂
I know it sounds crazy,
她说她将会变革公司的
She said she's going to change the company
运作方式
In the way it operates.
然后呢  公司以后采取非暴力政策了
So what, the company's gonna go nonviolent now?
-听我说完  -告诉你  她在撒谎
- Just hear me out. - I'm telling you. I think she's lying.
这是从教堂拿来的  某种凭证之类的
It's from the church. Some kind of credential.
那里还有一些自动武器
There were some automatic weapons in there, too.
相信我  一看到假证件和武器
And trust me, if there's fake IDs and weapons
就知道肯定会有什么大事要发生
Something big's about to go down.
你妈妈
Your mom,
她说两天之后
She said after two days,
会作出变革
That's when she would make the change.
对
Yeah.
看看卡上的日期
Take a look at the date on that laminate,
也是两天
Two days away.
你认为这只是巧合吗  拜托
You think that's just a coincidence? come on,
林卡  你犯不着惊讶
Lincoln, you can't be surprised
一个抛家弃子的女人 现在也会撒谎
That a woman that would abandon her kids Would be less than truthful
影藏真实意图
About her intentions right now.
-你去哪里  -我要找她谈
- Hey, where you going? - I need to talk to her.
等等  我们仔细分析一下
Just take a moment. Let's figure this out.
如果她想领导公司
If she's looking to head the company,
我们必须有比单枪匹马
There has to a more realistic plan than a one-man
更现实的计划
Frontal assault.
她会听我的
She'll listen to me.
她叫你不要回去了  林肯
She asked you not to come back, Linc.
这就是警告
That's a warning.
林肯回广场了
Lincoln's back at the plaza.
我觉得我们必须
I think we need
认识到他比我们
To realize he's more of a threat
设想中更具威胁
Than we gave him credit for.
他找到那栋大厦了
He found the mansion.
他的人在教堂找到了藏匿物
His guys got the stash at the church.
他不会收手的
He's not going to stop.
我告诉过他不要搅和的
I told him to stay away.
克里斯汀娜
Christina,
我们正待命击毙
We have a clean shot.
击毙
Take it.